Usage patterns for data tends to change over time.
数据的使用模式趋向于随时间变化
For data created today,
对于今天创建的数据
it is most likely accessed today.
今天最有可能被访问
It is less likely it'll be accessed next week.
不太可能下周就会被访问
Even less likely that is will be accessed next month,
更不可能在下个月被访问
and a year from now,
一年之后
it's unlikely it'll be accessed with any frequency, generally speaking.
它不太可能以任何频率进入
In many cases, we could save lots of money by having
在很多情况下 我们可以省下很多钱
S3 objects change their storage tiers over time.
S3 对象在一段时间内更改其存储层
This is what S3 lifecycle policies allow us to do.
这是 S3 生命周期策略允许我们做的事情
You define a lifecycle policy on a bucket
在存储区上定义生命周期策略
and what action should happen over what period of time.
以及什么行动应该在一段时间内发生
You could have an object stay in standard storage for
您可以将对象停留在标准存储器中
three months and then moved to infrequently
三个月后
access storage for a year and then to glacier.
进入仓库一年然后再到冰川
You can also do this for only certain types of objects in
您也可以仅对某些类型的对象执行此
a bucket or for certain subsections within a bucket.
存储区或存储区中的某些子段
Another option you have is to just delete an object after certain amount of time.
另一个选项是在一定时间后删除对象
There is no cheaper storage than not storing at all.
没有比存储更便宜的存储器
As we store more and more data from more and more sources,
随着我们越来越多地存储越来越多的数据
it's important to consider how your data storage cost will grow over time and when
重要的是考虑您的数据存储成本将随着时间和时间的推移而增加
the cost of storing data exceeds
存储数据的成本超过
the value of being able to access it if you would ever need it.
能够访问它的值 ( 如果您需要的话 )
S3 events allow you to take action when things happen in your S3 buckets.
S3 事件允许您在 S3 存储区中发生事情时执行操作
For example, S3 events allow you to run
例如  S3 事件允许您运行
a Lambda function on the activity of objects in your S3 bucket.
对 S3 存储区中的对象活动的 Lambda 函数
You could run a Lambda on the creation of any object.
您可以在创建任何对象时运行 Lambda
If you had a bucket that stored photos.
如果你有一个存储照片的桶
When a photo were uploaded to that bucket and S3 event could trigger
将照片上载到该存储区时  S3 事件可能触发
a Lambda function to go and create multiple resolutions of that photo.
a Lambda 函数 用于创建该照片的多个分辨率
S3 events have many potential uses.
S3 事件具有许多潜在用途
That photo scenario is a example of a common use case,
该照片场景是常见用例的示例
decoupling file uploading from power processing.
将文件上载与电源处理进行解耦
You can turn on versioning for an S3 bucket.
您可以打开 S3 存储区的版本控制
This thing keeps every version of an object.
这个东西保留着一个物体的每个版本
So if you upload a document to S3,
所以如果你把文件上传到 S3
then modify it and then modify it again,
然后修改它然后再修改它
S3 keeps three copies of that object.
S3 保留该对象的三个副本
To your application, it will look like there is
对你的申请 它看起来就好像有
just one object that has your most recent changes.
只有一个对象具有最新的更改
But if you dig into the details of the object,
但如果你挖掘物体的细节
you will see that S3 is holding on to all copies of that object.
您将看到 S3 正在保存该对象的所有副本
With versioning turned on,
在已开启版本控制的情况下
you can delete an object and it will disappear from your bucket,
你可以删除一个物体它就会从你的桶里消失
but it will not be gone.
但它不会消失
S3 uses what it calls delete markers to allow you to even recover deleted objects.
S3 使用它调用的删除标记来允许您甚至恢复已删除的对象
This functionality allows you to have a safety net under your S3 buckets.
此功能允许您在 S3 存储区下具有安全网
Accidental changes can be undone.
意外更改可以撤销
You can go back at any time and see what the original version of an object look like.
您可以随时返回并查看对象的原始版本是什么样的
If a system became compromised by attackers and they try to run
如果一个系统被攻击者破坏 他们试图运行
a ransomware attack where they encrypted all of
一个勒索软件攻击
your files and wanted you to pay for the encryption key,
你的文件要求你支付加密密钥
you could calmly revert all of the objects
你可以平静地还原所有
back to the last version and go on with your day.
回到最后的版本继续你的日子